

ELDAR GAZIZOV

PYTHON SOFTWARE ENGINEER

+420777442357 kursus1010@gmail.com U Elektrárny, Prague, 170 00, Czechia

SKILLS

Web Development (Back-End)

Web Development (Front-End)

Data Engineering

Data Analysis

Machine Learning

Python

C/C++

Javascript

HTML

CSS

LINKS

GitHub:

http://github.com/bigbossguru

LinkedIn

http://linkedin.com/in/eldar-gazizo

Upwork:

http://upwork.com/freelancers/~0 16e50343c578150bf

LANGUAGES

Czech
Russian

ABOUT ME

Software Engineer with more than 4 years of experience in development. I'm passionate about creating quality digital products that meet all of the customer's needs. I believe my experience has allowed me to hone my attention to detail and critical thinking skills as well as enhance my communication skills. I'm excited to apply my technical skills to develop applications and systems.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

AKKODIS CZ S.R.O. | PRAGUE JUN 2022-PRESENT

Currently, I'm working as a Senior Software Engineer. In the last half of the year, I work on a project for automotive, I'm developing a KPI tool that provides receiving data from different sensors and cameras from the car and then makes cleaning synchronized and preprocessing data after that makes calculating and next analyzing data. That tool evaluates the measuring quality from sensors and reports all deviations.

Skills: Python, NumPy, Pandas, Django, FastAPI, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Docker, ML, Matplotlib, Pytest, Javascript, HTML, CSS, ReactJS, ElasticSearch

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

AKKODIS CZ S.R.O. | PRAGUE DEC 2021-JUN 2022

I've been working as a Software Engineer. My responsibility included web development, modeling database architecture, testing, and maintaining the oldest projects.

Skills: Python, NumPy, Pandas, Django, FastAPI, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Docker, ML, Matplotlib, Pytest, Javascript, HTML, CSS, ReactJS

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

ELEKTROLINE INC. | PRAGUE FEB 2020 - DEC 2021

Extended my responsibility which includes designing and implementing special tools for testing and analyzing data and storing it in a database in Python.

Skills: C/C++, Python, NumPy, Pandas, SSH, Django, SQL, HTML, CSS, JS

PLC PROGRAMMER

ELEKTROLINE INC. | PRAGUE FEB 2019 - FEB 2020

I've worked as a PLC Programmer. Design and development of control programs for railway transportation. Designing a visual HMI panel for interaction and optimization of different settings.

Skills: C/C++, HMI, B&R PLC, Automation Studio

EDUCATION

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

CZECH TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY IN PRAGUE | PRAGUE 2018

Information and Automation Technology

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

FUEL AND ENERGY COLLEGE IN UFA | UFA 2013

Power stations networks and systems